(Sheldon:)...it's my bedtime, so whatever
gets you out the door. Good night.
(Bernadette:)Howie, I'm back!
(Howard:)I just got her to sleep.
(Howard:)Sorry.
(Howard:)What took you so long?
The grocery store's a few blocks away.
They only had regular yogurt.
I had to go to a different store
(Bernadette:)to get the extra-fat kind
your mom likes.
(Howard:)Then why do I smell coffee
on your breath?
(Bernadette:)So what? After two days
of taking care of her,
(Bernadette:)excuse me for stopping
to get a mocha.
(Howard:)A mocha?
Well, it must be nice to be queen.
(Bernadette:)Queen?
I've been killing myself here!
(Howard:)Well, whose fault is that? I wanted
to get a nurse, but you were all,
"I'm nice. I want to take care of people."
(Bernadette:)I'm glad I got that mocha.
And you know what else I'm glad about?
(Bernadette:)I bought you a brownie
and I ate it in the car!
Howard!
(Howard:)Thanks a lot.
Now I have to go rub her belly again.